Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2016
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher coaches Ensemble Uusinta members Malla Vivolin, Max Savikangas, and Maria Puusaari, glass bottles on Eimermacher's Transparenz at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4187 TRANSPARENZ by Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_116.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher coaches Ensemble Uusinta members Malla Vivolin and Max Savikangas, glass bottles on Eimermacher's Transparenz at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4188 rehearsal with composer Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_117.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher coaches Ensemble Uusinta members Malla Vivolin, Max Savikangas, and Maria Puusaari, glass bottles on Eimermacher's Transparenz at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4189rehearsal with Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_118.tif)
- Ensemble Uusinta members Malla Vivolin, Max Savikangas, and Maria Puusaari, glass bottles rehearse Hanna Eimermacher's Transparenz at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4190Transparenz by Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_119.tif)
- Ensemble Uusinta members Malla Vivolin, Max Savikangas, and Maria Puusaari, glass bottles rehearse Hanna Eimermacher's Transparenz at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4191 TRANSPARENZ by Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_120.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars rehearses Chinary Ung's Oracle with Ensemble Uusinta (Jonathan Hepfer, percussion, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Maria Puusaari, violin, Malla Vivolin, flute, and Marko Portin, clarinet) at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4197rehearsal Ensemble Uusinta.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_121.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars rehearses Chinary Ung's Oracle with Ensemble Uusinta members Pinja Laine, violoncello, Maria Puusaari, violin at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4198 rehearsal Emsemble Uusinta.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_122.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars rehearses Chinary Ung's Oracle with Ensemble Uusinta members Pinja Laine, violoncello, Maria Puusaari, violin at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4199rehearsal Emsemble Uusinta.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_123.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars rehearses Chinary Ung's Oracle with Ensemble Uusinta members Pinja Laine, violoncello, Maria Puusaari, violin at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4201rehearsal conductor Jozsef Hars.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_124.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars rehearses Chinary Ung's Oracle with Ensemble Uusinta members Pinja Laine, violoncello, Maria Puusaari, violin at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4202 copy.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_125.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars rehearses Chinary Ung's Oracle with Ensemble Uusinta members Pinja Laine, violoncello, Maria Puusaari, violin at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4219conductor Jozsef Hars Ensemble Uusinta.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_126.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars rehearses Chinary Ung's Oracle with Ensemble Uusinta member Maria Puusaari, violin at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4224conductor Jozsef Hars Emsemble Uusinta.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_127.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars rehearses Chinary Ung's Oracle with Ensemble Uusinta (Marko Portin, clarinet, Jonathan Hepfer, percussion, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Maria Puusaari, violin, and Malla Vivolin, flute) at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4246Ensemble Uusinta.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_128.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches Jozsef Hars, conductor and Malla Vivolin, flute of Ensemble Uusinta on Ung's Oracle at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4249composer Chinary Ung Rnsemble Uusinta.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_129.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars leading Ensemble Uusinta in rehearsal of Chinary Ung's Oracle at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4250COMPOSER jOZSEF hARS.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_130.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaching conductor Jozsef Hars of Ensemble Uusinta on Ung's Oracle at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4252composer ChinaryUng and conductor Joszef Hars .tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_131.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaching Ensemble Uusinta on Ung's Oracle at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4254composer Chinary UNG.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_132.tif)
- Composer Chinary Ung coaches Jozsef Hars, conductor, and Ensemble Uusinta (John Smigielski, percussion, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Marko Portin, clarinet, Maria Puusaari, violin, and Malla Vivolin, flute) on Ung's Oracle at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4255 composer Chinary UNG.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_133.tif)
- Student composer Nathan Kelly coaches Katie Schoepflin, clarinet of Ensemble Dal Niente on Kelly's Of Leaves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4261athan Kelly Leaves.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_134.tif)
- Student composer Nathan Kelly coaches Michael Lewanski, conductor and Ensemble Dal Niente members (Tam Travers, violin and Emma Hospelhorn, flute) on Kelly's Of Leaves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4266 Nathan Kelly and Ensemble Dal Niente.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_135.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski leading Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Tam Travers, violin, Chris Wild, violoncello, and Greg Beyer, percussion) on Nathan Kelly's Of Leaves at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4267Ensemble Dal Niente student composer concert.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_136.tif)
- Student composer Ioannis Angelakis coaching Mabel Kwan, piano of Ensemble Dal Niente on Angelakis' piece Dreamplay (III) at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4268student composer with Ensemble Dal Niente.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_137.tif)
- Student composer Joungbum Lee coaches Chris Wild, violoncello of Ensemble Dal Niente on Lee's piece Relatum at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4272student composer.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_138.tif)
- Student composer Joungbum Lee coaches Ensemble Dal Niente members Tam Travers, violin and Chris Wild, violoncello on Lee's Relatum at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4274Ensemble Dal Niente student composer.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_139.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski and Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Tam Travers, violin, Greg Beyer, percussion, and Chris Wild, violoncello) performing student compositions at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4275ENSEMBLE DAL NIENTE.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_140.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski and Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Greg Beyer, percussion, Tam Travers, violin, and Chris Wild, violoncello) performing student compositions at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4276 ENSEMBLE DAL NIENTE.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_141.tif)
- Tam Travers, violin, Mabel Kwan, piano, and Emma Hospelhorn, flute of Ensemble Dal Niente performing student composer Ville Raasakka's Vanitas at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Nathan Kelly Leaves with Ensemble Dal Niente.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_142.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski and Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Tam Travers, violin, Greg Beyer, percussion, and Chris Wild, violoncello) performing student compositions at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4279 copy.jpg Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_143.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski and Ensemble Dal Niente (Mabel Kwan, piano, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Tam Travers, violin, Greg Beyer, percussion, and Chris Wild, violoncello) performing student compositions at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4279.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_144.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski and Ensemble Dal Niente (Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Mabel Kwan, piano, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Tam Travers, violin, Greg Beyer, percussion, and Chris Wild, violoncello) acknowledging applause at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4280 copy.jpg Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_145.tif)
- Conductor Michael Lewanski and Ensemble Dal Niente (Katie Schoepflin, clarinet, Mabel Kwan, piano, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Tam Travers, violin, Greg Beyer, percussion, and Chris Wild, violoncello) acknowledging applause at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4280.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_146.tif)
- Malla Vivolin, Max Savikangas, and Maria Puusaari, glass bottles of Ensemble Uusinta perform Hanna Eimermacher's Transparenz at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4287 TRANSPARENZ by Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_147.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars leads Ensemble Uusinta (Malla Vivolin, flute, John Smigielski, percussion, Maria Puusaari, violin, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Jonathan Hepfer, percussion, and Marko Portin, clarinet) in a performance at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4292.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_148.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars leads Ensemble Uusinta (John Smigielski, percussion, Malla Vivolin, flute, Maria Puusaari, violin, Jonathan Hepfer, percussion, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Marko Portin, clarinet, and Alexander Chimienti, percussion) in a performance of Chinary Ung's Oracle at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4310.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_149.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars acknowledges composer Chinary Ung along with Ensemble Uusinta (John Smigielski, percussion, Malla Vivolin, flute, Maria Puusaari, violin, Jonathan Hepfer, percussion, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Marko Portin, clarinet, and Alexander Chimienti, percussion) after a performance of Ung's Oracle at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4311Ensemble Uusinta composer Chinary Ung.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_150.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars acknowledges composer Chinary Ung along with Ensemble Uusinta (John Smigielski, percussion, Malla Vivolin, flute, Maria Puusaari, violin, Jonathan Hepfer, percussion, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Marko Portin, clarinet, and Alexander Chimienti, percussion) after a performance of Ung's Oracle at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4313 ComposerChinary Ung Ensemble UUsinta.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_151.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars leads Ensemble Uusinta (Väinö Jalkanen, piano, Maria Puusaari, violin, John Smigielski, percussion, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Marko Portin, clarinet, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Jonathan Hepfer, percussion) in a performance of Joshua Fineberg's Objects trouvés at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4315Ensemble Uusinta playing Joshua Fineberg Objects trouves (2009).tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_152.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars acknowledges composer Joshua Fineberg along with Ensemble Uusinta (Väinö Jalkanen, piano, Maria Puusaari, violin, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Marko Portin, clarinet, John Smigielski, percussion, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Jonathan Hepfer, percussion) in a performance of Joshua Fineberg's Objects trouvés at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4318 Ensemble Uusinta composer Joahua Fineberg.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_153.tif)
- Conductor Jozsef Hars acknowledges composer Joshua Fineberg along with Ensemble Uusinta (Väinö Jalkanen, piano, Maria Puusaari, violin, Emma Hospelhorn, flute, Marko Portin, clarinet, John Smigielski, percussion, Pinja Laine, violoncello, Jonathan Hepfer, percussion) in a performance of Joshua Fineberg's Objects trouvés at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Ensemble Uusinta composer Josuha Fineberg Objects trouves (2009).tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_154.tif)
- Malla Vivolin, bass flute and Marko Kassl, accordion of Ensemble Uusinta perform Hanna Eimermacher's Kannst du diesen verkehrt fliegenden Vogel sehen? at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4324Malla Vivolin flute Ensemble Uusinta.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_155.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher acknowledges applause with Malla Vivolin, bass flute and Marko Kassl, accordion after a performance of Eimermacher's Kannst du diesen verkehrt fliegenden Vogel sehen? at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name composer Hanna Eimermacher copy.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_156.tif)
- Composer Hanna Eimermacher acknowledges applause with Malla Vivolin, bass flute and Marko Kassl, accordion after a performance of Eimermacher's Kannst du diesen verkehrt fliegenden Vogel sehen? at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4332 composer Hanna Eimermacher.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_157.tif)
- Composer Joshua Fineberg coaches the Arditti Quartet (Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Irvine Arditti, violin, and Ralf Ehlers, viola) on Fineberg's La Quintana for string quartet and electronics at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4336composer Joshua Fineberg.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_158.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen coaches Brad Lubman, conductor of Ensemble Signal, on Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4339brad Lubman composer Hans Abrahamsen.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_159.tif)
- Composer Hans Abrahamsen coaches Brad Lubman, conductor of Ensemble Signal, on Abrahamsen's Schnee at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4341composer Hans Abrahamsen Brad Lubman.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_160.tif)
- Matt Sargent, sound engineer, and J.T. Rinker and Olivier Pasquet, electronics rehearse David Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4343.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_161.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Ralf Ehlers, viola, Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, and Irvine Arditti, violin) on Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4349.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_162.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, and Irvine Arditti, violin) on Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4350.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_163.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Ralf Ehlers, viola, Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, and Irvine Arditti, violin) on Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4351.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_164.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Ralf Ehlers, viola, Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, and Irvine Arditti, violin) on Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4352.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_165.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Ralf Ehlers, viola, Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, and Irvine Arditti, violin) on Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4353.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_166.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Ralf Ehlers, viola, Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, and Irvine Arditti, violin) on Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4354.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_167.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Ralf Ehlers, viola and Irvine Arditti, violin) on Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4356comp[oser David Felder Arditti Quartet.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_168.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches members of the Arditti Quartet (Ashot Sarkissjan and Irvine Arditti, violin) on Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4357.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_169.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ralf Ehlers, viola) on Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4359.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_170.tif)
- Composer David Felder coaches the Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, violin, Ashot Sarkissjan, violin, Lucas Fels, violoncello, Ralf Ehlers, viola) on Felder's Netivot at June in Buffalo 2016, 2016_06_09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_4360.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0079_171.tif)